[Intro]
[sustained vocal hum with heavy reverb]
[clean electric guitar arpeggio enters]
[orchestral strings swell]
[Verse 1]
[baritone male vocals]
يا دار ميّة بالعلياء فالسند
أقوت وطال عليها سالف الأبد
[distorted electric guitar power chords enter]
يا دار ميّة بالعلياء فالسند
أقوت وطال عليها سالف الأبد
[Chorus]
[full band enters, driving drums]
وقفت فيها أصيلانا أسائلها
عيّت جوابا وما بالربع من أحد
إلا الأواريّ لأيا ما أبيّنها
والنؤي كالحوض بالمظلومة الجلد
[Verse 2]
[half-time feel, bass and drums continue]
ردّت عليه أقاصيه ولبّده
ضرب الوليدة بالمسحاة في الثأد
خلّت سبيل أتيّ كان يحبسه
ورفّعته إلى السجفين فالنضد
[Chorus]
[full energy, distorted guitar riffs]
أضحت خلاء وأضحى أهلها احتملوا
أخنى عليها الذي أخنى على لبد
[Guitar Solo]
[melodic electric guitar solo with Middle Eastern phrasing and fast runs]
[Bridge]
[clean guitar arpeggio, strings pad]
فعدّ عما ترى إذ لا ارتجاع له
وانم القتود على عيرانة أجد
[vocal intensity increases]
مقذوفة بدخيس النحض بازلها
له صريف صريف القعو بالمسد
[Chorus]
[climax, heavy drums and distorted guitars]
أضحت خلاء وأضحى أهلها احتملوا
أخنى عليها الذي أخنى على لبد
[Outro]
[guitar solo continues over fading rhythm section]
[vocal ad-libs: ah-ah-ah]
[final power chord ring out]
مقذوفة بدخيس النحض بازلها
له صريف صريف القعو بالمسد
[drums end with a final crash]